[
        {
        "topic" : "html",
        "front" : "This is the element tag used to create a line break",
        "back" :   "<br>"
        },
        {
        "topic": "html",
        "front": "This element tag is for images",
        "back":   "<img>"
        },
        {
        "topic": "html",
        "front": "The attribute within an <a> tag that contains the link.",
        "back":   "href"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "html",
        "front" : "This tag defines a thematic break in an HTML page.",
        "back" :   "<hr>"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "html",
        "front" : "The html tag for text that has a strike-through",
        "back" :   "<del>"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "css",
        "front" : "The name for the first part of a CSS rule-set",
        "back" :   "selector"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "css",
        "front" : "The name for the second part of a CSS rule-set",
        "back" :   "declaration"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "css",
        "front" : "Use this type of style to apply a unique style for a single element.",
        "back" :   "inline"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "css",
        "front" : "Name for a color value specified in the following format: #RRGGBB",
        "back" :   "hexadecimal"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "css",
        "front" : "This CSS property specifies whether to clip content or to add scrollbars if an element too big" ,
        "back" :   "overflow"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "javascript",
        "front" : "This operator returns the remainder of a division" ,
        "back" :   "modulus"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "javascript",
        "front" : "The name for a name-object pair in a Javascript Object." ,
        "back" :   "property"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "javascript",
        "front" : "This Javascript string method extracts part of a string and returns the extracted part in a new string" ,
        "back" :   "slice()"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "javascript",
        "front" : "This javascript array creates a new array by merging existing arrays" ,
        "back" :   "concat()"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "javascript",
        "front" : "This Javascript data type represents one of two values: true or false" ,
        "back" :   "boolean"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "node",
        "front" : "This is the command to include the built-in file system module" ,
        "back" :   "var fs = require('fs');"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "node",
        "front" : "This method is used to read files on your machine asyncrhonously." ,
        "back" :   "fs.readFile()"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "node",
        "front" : "To enable node to transfer data over the hyper text transfer protocol, you would type this command" ,
        "back" :   "var http = require('http');"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "node",
        "front" : "This node file is essentially a manifest about applications, packages, modules, etc." ,
        "back" :   "package.json"
        },
        {
        "topic" : "node",
        "front" : "You can send email directly from you machine by installing this node module" ,
        "back" :   "nodemailer"
        }
]
